Guide to the New York University Archives Biographical Files MC.317
New York University Archives
- Chandler, Dr. Bruce, undated (Box 36)
- Chandless, Jr. George B., undated (Box 36)
- Chananau, Alexander '41 L, undated (Box 36)
- Chang, David C., undated (Box 36)
- Chang, (Change), Kathleen, undated (Box 36)
- Chang, Kit, undated (Box 36)
- Chang, Robert, undated (Box 36)
- Chang, Sheldon S., undated (Box 36)
- Chaniotis, Angelos, undated (Box 36)
- Chapin, Albert F., undated (Box 36)
- Chaplin, Gloria, undated (Box 36)
- Chaplin, Hugh, undated (Box 36)
- Chapman, Chalmers Durand (1845 - 1931), undated (Box 36)
- Chandra, Kanchan (Professor), undated (Box 36)
- Chapman, Gloria, undated (Box 36)
- Chapman, H., undated (Box 36)
- Chapman, Dr. Harmon M., undated (Box 36)
- Chapman, Herrick Easton, undated (Box 36)
- Chapnick, Howard, undated (Box 36)
- Charap, Bertran W., undated (Box 36)
- Charipper, Harry A., undated (Box 36)
- Charles, Irene M., undated (Box 36)
- Charry, Jonathan M., undated (Box 36)
- Chaudhuri, Una, undated (Box 36)
- Chase, David, undated (Box 36)
- Chase, Deborah, undated (Box 36)
- Chase, Harry Woodburn, undated (Box 37)
- Chase, Lucetta Crum (Mrs. Harry W. Chase), undated (Box 37)
- Chase, Oscar G., undated (Box 37)
- Chase, Randolph (Dr.), undated (Box 37)
- Chase, Stanley, undated (Box 37)
- Chasis, Herbert, undated (Box 37)
- Chaudhry, Anand, undated (Box 37)
- Chaves, Marta (FAS), undated (Box 38)
- Chazan, Robert, undated (Box 38)
- Chazen, Geoffrey D., M.D., undated (Box 38)
- Chein, Isidor, undated (Box 38)
- Chelkowski, Peter, undated (Box 38)
- Chen, Guangcheng, undated (Box 38)
- Chen, Shi-Zheng, undated (Box 38)
- Cheo, Dr. Bernard Ru-Shao, undated (Box 38)
- Cherkezian, Nazaret, undated (Box 38)
- Cherne, Leo '34W, undated (Box 38)
- Chernichaw, Mark, undated (Box 38)
- Cherny, George V., undated (Box 38)
- Cherry, James R. Esq., undated (Box 38)
- Cheshire, Godfrey, undated (Box 38)
- Chess, Stella, undated (Box 38)
- Cheswell, William T., undated (Box 38)
- Cheung, Tan Yee, undated (Box 38)
- Chevigny, Paul G., undated (Box 38)
- Chiarelli, Sabino, undated (Box 38)
- Chicoye, Jr. Max, undated (Box 38)
- Childress, Robert D., undated (Box 38)
- Childs, Marquis, undated (Box 38)
- Chilton, Neal W., undated (Box 38)
- Chinna, May Edward, undated (Box 38)
- Chin, Wan-Cheng, undated (Box 38)
- Chisholm, David, undated (Box 38)
- Choi, Frederick D.S., undated (Box 38)
- Chog, Christine, undated (Box 38)
- Chow, Dao-Yi, undated (Box 38)
- Christ-Janer, Albert, undated (Box 38)
- Christian, Joseph, undated (Box 38)
- Christensen, L. Royal, undated (Box 38)
- Christensen, T.G.S., undated (Box 38)
- Christensson, James, undated (Box 38)
- Christgau, Georgia, undated (Box 38)
- Christiani, Enus, undated (Box 38)
- Christie, John Richard, undated (Box 38)
- Christopher, Nicholas (FAS), undated (Box 38)
- Chronis, Constantine, undated (Box 38)
- Chu, Ju Tang, undated (Box 38)
- Chubet, Thomas D. '72, undated (Box 38)
- Chuck D (Public Enemy), undated (Box 38)
- Chung, Young Yang, undated (Box 38)
- Church, Austin F., undated (Box 38)
- Churchill, Angiola, undated (Box 38)
- Chusid, Anita Beverly, undated (Box 38)
- Chusid, Martin, undated (Box 38)
- Chute, Charlton P., undated (Box 38)
- Chwast, Jacob, undated (Box 38)
- Cipolla, Vivian, undated (Box 38)
- Ciulei, Liviu, undated (Box 38)
- Cicchino, Peter M., undated (Box 38)
- Claman, Irving, undated (Box 38)
- Claps, Bernadette, undated (Box 38)
- Clarence, Ashley, undated (Box 38)
- Clark, Bernice W., undated (Box 38)
- Clark, Bradford, undated (Box 38)
- Clark, C.C., undated (Box 38)
- Clark, Clifford D., undated (Box 38)
- Clark, Eugenie, undated (Box 38)
- Clark, George T., undated (Box 38)
- Clark, Harold E., undated (Box 38)
- Clark, John H. '65G., undated (Box 38)
- Clark, Kenneth, undated (Box 38)
- Clark, Kierstie, undated (Box 38)
- Clark, Leroy David, undated (Box 39)
- Clark, Lincoln, undated (Box 39)
- Clark, Mrs. Wallace, undated (Box 39)
- Clark, Tom C., undated (Box 39)
- Clark, Richard G. '60, undated (Box 39)
- Clark, William J., undated (Box 39)
- Clarke, Griffith X. '71 C., undated (Box 39)
- Clarke, John Henrik, undated (Box 39)
- Clarke, Shirley, undated (Box 39)
- Clary, Rhoda Lipp '80 L., undated (Box 39)
- Claster, Jill '52W, '54G, Dram WSUC, undated (Box 39)
- Claus, Geroge, undated (Box 39)
- Clausen, Robert W., undated (Box 39)
- Clausman, Gilbert J., undated (Box 39)
- Clay, David M., undated (Box 39)
- Clayman, Lawrence H. (Dental), undated (Box 39)
- Clements, Millard, undated (Box 39)
- Clements, Robert J., undated (Box 39)
- Clements, Sumi, undated (Box 39)
- Clevenger, Helen, undated (Box 39)
- Clewig, Marlene, undated (Box 39)
- Clifford, James, undated (Box 39)
- Clift, Virgil A., undated (Box 39)
- Climent, Elena, undated (Box 39)
- Clinton, Bill, undated (Box 39)
- Clinton, Chelsea, undated (Box 39)
- Clinton, Hillary, undated (Box 39)
- Clooney, Amal, undated (Box 39)
- Clubb, O. Edmond, undated (Box 39)
- Clurman, Herman, undated (Box 39)
- Clurman, Robert, undated (Box 39)
- Clyne, James F., undated (Box 39)
- Coakley, George W., undated (Box 39)
- Cochran, Thomas C., undated (Box 39)
- Cockling, Walter D., undated (Box 39)
- Cody, Mildred, undated (Box 39)
- Coe, Barbara, undated (Box 39)
- Coelho, David H., undated (Box 39)
- Coen, James, undated (Box 39)
- Coen, Joel, undated (Box 39)
- Cofer, Dr. Charles N., undated (Box 39)
- Coffey, J. Russell, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Arthur, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Frank, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Hayyim, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Herbert, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Jack J. '81W, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Dr. Jacob, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Julius Henry, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Dr. Kalman J., undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Larry '79 GBA, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Leonard, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Lizabeth, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Melvin, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Mildred, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Mitchell, undated (Box 39)
- Cohen, Morris, undated (Box 40)
- Cohen, Phil '57G, undated (Box 40)
- Cohen, Phil H. '57C, undated (Box 40)
- Cohen, Robert, undated (Box 40)
- Cohen, Sonora '56, '58, undated (Box 40)
- Cohen, Sheldon G. '43D, undated (Box 40)
- Cohen, Stephen, undated (Box 40)
- Cohen, Youssef, undated (Box 40)
- Cohen-Solal, Annie, undated (Box 40)
- Cohlan, Sidney, undated (Box 40)
- Cohn, Harry M., undated (Box 40)
- Cohoes, Richard C., undated (Box 40)
- Colahan, Stephen J., undated (Box 40)
- Coldstream, Sir George, undated (Box 40)
- Cole, Beatrice L., undated (Box 40)
- Cole, Ellen L. '67 A., undated (Box 40)
- Cole, Johnetta, undated (Box 40)
- Cole, Joyce, undated (Box 40)
- Coleman, Alexander, undated (Box 40)
- Coleman, Corrine Grad, undated (Box 40)
- Coleman, John, undated (Box 40)
- Coleman, Margaret M., undated (Box 40)
- Coleman, Peter, undated (Box 40)
- Coler, Myron A., undated (Box 40)
- Coles, Jerome S., undated (Box 40)
- Coles, Geraldine Hunt '35 WSC., undated (Box 40)
- Colin, David H., undated (Box 40)
- Collins, Christopher, undated (Box 40)
- Collins, Daniel G., undated (Box 40)
- Collins, Donald, undated (Box 40)
- Collins, G. Rollan, undated (Box 40)
- Collins, Perry McDonough, undated (Box 40)
- Collins, W.D., undated (Box 40)
- Colston, James A., undated (Box 40)
- Colt, Samuel, undated (Box 40)
- Colvin, Elinor, undated (Box 41)
- Combes, Frank Charles, undated (Box 41)
- Comden, Bette, undated (Box 41)
- Comden, Betty (Kyle) '37 Ed., undated (Box 41)
- Comito, Nicholas, undated (Box 41)
- Commager, Henry Steele, undated (Box 41)
- Comstock, George A., undated (Box 41)
- Conant, Howard S., undated (Box 41)
- Colesberry, Robert, undated (Box 40)
- Conant, James, undated (Box 41)
- Conaway Jr. O.B., undated (Box 41)
- Condit, John L., undated (Box 41)
- Conforti, James '37 E, undated (Box 41)
- Conklin Jr. dr. George T. '43 GBA, undated (Box 41)
- Connell, Noreen '76 TSOA, undated (Box 41)
- Connelly, Joan, undated (Box 41)
- Connelly, William F., undated (Box 41)
- Conner, Harold A., undated (Box 41)
- Connery, Joseph, undated (Box 41)
- Connolly, John M., undated (Box 41)
- Connor, James (SEHNAP), undated (Box 41)
- Connor, John, undated (Box 41)
- Connors, Michael, undated (Box 41)
- Conroy, David P., undated (Box 41)
- Consolo, Faith Hope, undated (Box 41)
- Constantine, Gus, undated (Box 41)
- Contini, Renato, undated (Box 41)
- Converse, John Marquis, undated (Box 41)
- Conley, Dalton, undated (Box 41)
- Convit, Antonio, undated (Box 41)
- Cook, Alice Rice, undated (Box 41)
- Cook, Frederick Albert, undated (Box 41)
- Cook, Stuart W., undated (Box 41)
- Cook, Walter W.S., undated (Box 41)
- Cooley, Elizabeth F., undated (Box 41)
- Cooley, Hollis R., undated (Box 41)
- Cooley, Jean P., undated (Box 41)
- Cooley, Robert E., undated (Box 41)
- Cooley, Rita W., undated (Box 41)
- Cooley, Thomas, undated (Box 41)
- Coombes, Orde, undated (Box 41)
- Coonradt, Arthur C., undated (Box 41)
- Coons, Edgar, undated (Box 41)
- Cooper, Chester, undated (Box 41)
- Cooper, Dennis, undated (Box 41)
- Cooper, Dr. Irving S., undated (Box 42)
- Cooper, Louis, undated (Box 42)
- Cooper, May, undated (Box 42)
- Coox, Alvin D., undated (Box 42)
- Copeland, Amorita, undated (Box 42)
- Copeland, Jeremy Lee, undated (Box 42)
- Copeland, Melvin, undated (Box 42)
- Copperfield, David, undated (Box 42)
- Corbin, Arnold, undated (Box 42)
- Corbitt, Ted, undated (Box 42)
- Cordasco, Frank, undated (Box 42)
- Cornell, William B., undated (Box 42)
- Cornuelle, Richard, undated (Box 42)
- Coron, Howard, undated (Box 42)
- Corradi, Juan, undated (Box 42)
- Correa Maggin, Jane, undated (Box 42)
- Corren, Dean R., undated (Box 42)
- Corrigan, Robert W., undated (Box 42)
- Corson, Edward M., undated (Box 42)
- Cortes, Tara, undated (Box 42)
- Cortwright, Marguerite, undated (Box 42)
- Coruzzi, Gloria (FAS), undated (Box 42)
- Corwin, Ronald D., undated (Box 42)
- Corwin, Scott L. '81 GBA, undated (Box 42)
- Cosby, Bill, undated (Box 42)
- Cosell, Howard, undated (Box 42)
- Cosgrove, Jessica Garreton, undated (Box 42)
- Cosloy- Blank, Sharon, undated (Box 42)
- Cossart, Mollie M., undated (Box 42)
- Costagnaro, Anthony R., undated (Box 42)
- Costello, Elvis, undated (Box 42)
- Costello, Jane (Memorial Minute), undated (Box 42)
- Costello, Maurice, undated (Box 42)
- Costello, Timothy W., undated (Box 42)
- Coster, Ronald, undated (Box 42)
- Costikyan, Edward, undated (Box 42)
- Costonis, John J., undated (Box 42)
- Cotellessa, Dr. Robert, undated (Box 42)
- Cott, Betty, undated (Box 42)
- Cottrell Jr., Dr. Leonard S., undated (Box 42)
- Cotter, William E., undated (Box 42)
- Cotui, Dr., undated (Box 42)
- Coudenhove-Kalergi, Count Richard N., undated (Box 43)
- Coughlan, Joseph D., undated (Box 43)
- Courant, Richard, undated (Box 43)
- Cousin, Michelle, undated (Box 43)
- Coutts, Alan, undated (Box 43)
- Covey, Curt, undated (Box 43)
- Cowan, Robin, undated (Box 43)
- Cowee, Howard M., undated (Box 43)
- Cowie, Tim (Women's Volleyball Coach), undated (Box 43)
- Cox, Charles R., undated (Box 43)
- Cox, Glen, undated (Box 43)
- Cox, Philip W. L., undated (Box 43)
- Cox, Dr. Robert, undated (Box 43)
- Cox, Wade C., undated (Box 43)
- Cozzens, Henry A., undated (Box 43)
- Crabtree, Pam (FAS), undated (Box 43)
- Craddock, John, undated (Box 43)
- Crafts, Leland, undated (Box 43)
- Craig, C. Samuel, undated (Box 43)
- Cramp, Ralph E., undated (Box 43)
- Crane, Gerald C., undated (Box 43)
- Craven, Wesley Frank, undated (Box 43)
- Crawford, Adam, undated (Box 43)
- Crawford, Curtis, undated (Box 43)
- Crawford, Francis B., undated (Box 43)
- Creedon, John J. '55L, '52C., undated (Box 43)
- Crenshaw, Arlene, undated (Box 44)
- Cresson, Margaret French, N.A., undated (Box 44)
- Cricco, Nancy, undated (Box 44)
- Crisona, James J., undated (Box 44)
- Crist, William, undated (Box 44)
- Cristo-Loveanu, Elie, undated (Box 44)
- Crocker, Albert, undated (Box 44)
- Croly, Jennie June, undated (Box 44)
- Cromer, Earl of, undated (Box 44)
- Cronin, Anthony, undated (Box 44)
- Crosby, Ernest Howard, undated (Box 44)
- Crosby, Howard, undated (Box 44)
- Crosman, Arthur M., undated (Box 44)
- Cross, A.J. Foy, undated (Box 44)
- Cross, Gordon B., undated (Box 44)
- Crosse, Howard D., undated (Box 44)
- Crossett, Frederick Melvin, undated (Box 44)
- Crossland, Fred, undated (Box 45)
- Crow, Alice and Lester, undated (Box 45)
- Crow, Thomas, undated (Box 45)
- Crown, James T., undated (Box 45)
- Crudrup, Billy, undated (Box 45)
- Crum, Albert, undated (Box 45)
- Cruse, Harold, undated (Box 45)
- Crystal, Billy, undated (Box 45)
- Cukor, George, undated (Box 45)
- Culbertson, Rev. Michael Simpson, undated (Box 45)
- Cullen, Countee, undated (Box 45)
- Culley, Paul, undated (Box 45)
- Cullinan Giniger, Bernie, undated (Box 45)
- Cummings, Biondell, undated (Box 45)
- Cummings, Thos. S, undated (Box 45)
- Cuomo, Andrew, undated (Box 45)
- Cuomo, Mario, undated (Box 45)
- Curcio, Frances R., undated (Box 45)
- Curran, Frank J., undated (Box 45)
- Curtis, W. Redmond, undated (Box 45)
- Cusack, John, undated (Box 45)
- Cushman, Robert F., undated (Box 45)
- Cutler, Janice '34W, '46G., undated (Box 45)
- Cutter, Max Esq '34W, undated (Box 45)
- Cutler, Robert, undated (Box 45)
- Cutler, Stanley, undated (Box 45)
- Cutler, Suzanne '70G., undated (Box 45)
- Cutter, Walter A., undated (Box 45)
- Cypher, Irene F., undated (Box 45)
- Da Cal, Ernesto, undated (Box 45)
- D'Arcangelo, Rick A. '42 C, undated (Box 45)
- Dahlberg, Jane S., undated (Box 45)
- Dakins, J. Gordon, undated (Box 45)
- Dale, Harvey P., undated (Box 45)
- Dale, Ernest, undated (Box 46)
- Dale, John D. '34 GBA, undated (Box 46)
- Dale, Madeline McWhinney '47 GBA, undated (Box 46)
- Dales, Samuel, undated (Box 46)
- Dalton, Dr. H. Clark, undated (Box 46)
- Daly, Dorothy Bird, undated (Box 46)
- Daly, George, undated (Box 46)
- Daly, John F., undated (Box 46)
- Dana, Charles, undated (Box 46)
- Dancyger, Ken, undated (Box 46)
- Danielson, Paul A., undated (Box 46)
- Danielson, Virginia, undated (Box 46)
- Danza, Lorraine R. '82W, undated (Box 46)
- Da Ponte, Lorenzo L., undated (Box 46)
- Darden, Norman, undated (Box 46)
- Darling, Ron, undated (Box 46)
- Darlington, Charles G., undated (Box 46)
- Darlington, J.H. (James Henry), undated (Box 46)
- Darms, Lisa, undated (Box 46)
- Darrow, Tiger, undated (Box 46)
- D'Angelo, Savino, undated (Box 46)
- D'Asaro, Michael A. '60 C, undated (Box 46)
- Dashiell, Peggy Ann '71 GBA, undated (Box 46)
- Dasilva, Albert I. '42W, '52L., undated (Box 46)
- Dattner, Bernhard, undated (Box 46)
- Davachi, Lila, undated (Box 46)
- Davidson, Ben, undated (Box 46)
- Davidson, Dr. Carter, undated (Box 46)
- Davidson, Judge Irvin D., undated (Box 46)
- Davidson, Han. Irwin '27W, '29L., undated (Box 46)
- Davidson, Robert, undated (Box 46)
- Davidson, William, undated (Box 46)
- Davies, Capt. Thomas, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, Art, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, (General) Benjamin O. Jr., undated (Box 46)
- Davis, Charles, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, Clive J. '53W, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, Jeffrey P. '77, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, John, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, Marvin H. '47C, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, Martin, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, Ralph Currier, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, Thomas W., undated (Box 46)
- Davis, Victor, undated (Box 46)
- Davis, William Robert, undated (Box 46)
- Dawson, Alden B., undated (Box 46)
- Dawson, John J., undated (Box 46)
- Day, Ashley T., undated (Box 46)
- Dayton, Danny, undated (Box 46)
- Dean, Vera Michaels, undated (Box 46)
- Dean, Warren, undated (Box 46)
- De Bear Sue, undated (Box 46)
- De Blasio, Bill, undated (Box 46)
- DeBrovner, Charles H., undated (Box 46)
- DeCapriles, Jose, undated (Box 46)
- DeCapriles, Miguel A. '27W, '51G, 35L., undated (Box 47)
- DeCrescenzo, Steven '73W, '83D, undated (Box 47)
- DeCubas, Jose, undated (Box 47)
- Defendi, Vittorio, undated (Box 47)
- Degaetani, Jan, undated (Box 47)
- De Gonzales, Carmen A., undated (Box 47)
- De Gotari, Carlos Salinas, undated (Box 47)
- De Graff, Arthur C., undated (Box 47)
- De Harak, Rudolph, undated (Box 47)
- DeJoia, Alex, undated (Box 47)
- De Keersmaeker, Anne Teresa, undated (Box 47)
- Dejnozka, Prof. Edward L. '60Ed., undated (Box 47)
- Deland, Raymond J., undated (Box 47)
- Dellaverson, Gary, undated (Box 47)
- De Mille, Margaret, undated (Box 47)
- De Mille, Agnes, undated (Box 47)
- De Nerval, Gérard, undated (Box 47)
- De Niro, Robert, undated (Box 47)
- Denman, Elliot, undated (Box 192, Folder 15)
- Dennis, Walter (Episcopalian Bishop), undated (Box 47)
- Dent, Tory, undated (Box 47)
- De Pass, Steve, undated (Box 47)
- De Phillips, Frank A., undated (Box 47)
- De Quesada, Gonzalo (1891 Law), undated (Box 47)
- De Reineck, Marie, undated (Box 47)
- De Revere, E. Jon, undated (Box 47)
- Dr. De Rosis, Helen '53M, undated (Box 47)
- De Sanctis, Adolph, undated (Box 47)
- De Sloovere, Frederick J., undated (Box 47)
- DeSmitt, Vladimir, undated (Box 47)
- De Zafra, Carlos, undated (Box 47)
- De La Chappelle, Clarence E., undated (Box 47)
- DE La Girday, Veronique '76 G, undated (Box 47)
- Del Rio, Angel, undated (Box 47)
- Dean, Gene P., undated (Box 47)
- Dean, Leonard, undated (Box 47)
- Dean, Vera M., undated (Box 47)
- Deats, John R., undated (Box 47)
- Deery, Philip, undated (Box 47)
- Degen, Robert, undated (Box 47)
- Defendi, Vittorio, undated (Box 47)
- De Grazia, Alfred, undated (Box 47)
- Dejkunjorn, Vasit, undated (Box 47)
- Delafield, John and Edward, undated (Box 47)
- De Land, Colin, undated (Box 47)
- D'Elia, Matt, undated (Box 47)
- Delp, Wilbur C. Jr. '59L, undated (Box 47)
- Delsener, Ron '59 C., undated (Box 47)
- Deming, W. Edwards, undated (Box 47)
- Demier, Marvin C. '31E, undated (Box 47)
- De Montebello, Phillipe (buy Phillipe Lannes) '76 G, undated (Box 47)
- Dempsey, James '24L, undated (Box 47)
- Deng, Cora Yu-dji (Deng Yuzhi), undated (Box 47)
- Deng, Francis, undated (Box 47)
- De Nicola, Peter F. '76C, '78 GBA, undated (Box 47)
- Denkensohn, Michael '73, undated (Box 47)
- Dennis, Mary B (1st Woman PhD), undated (Box 47)
- Dennis, Walter, undated (Box 47)
- Dennison, Charles S., undated (Box 47)
- Denoon, David B.H., undated (Box 47)
- Densen-Gerber, Judianne '63M, undated (Box 48)
- Derby, Augustin, undated (Box 48)
- Deren, Maya, undated (Box 48)
- Derenberg, Walter J., undated (Box 48)
- Derounian, Stephen B., undated (Box 48)
- Derzon, Robert, undated (Box 48)
- DeSimone, Ralph '14E, undated (Box 48)
- Desmond, Charles S., undated (Box 48)
- Desravines, Jean D., undated (Box 48)
- Destine, Jean-Leon, undated (Box 48)
- Dettloff, Adolph M., undated (Box 48)
- Deutsch, Jonathan, undated (Box 48)
- Devine, Finbar, undated (Box 48)
- Devereaux, Jason, undated (Box 48)
- Devita, Christine, undated (Box 48)
- Dewey, Lloyd Ellis, undated (Box 48)
- Diamond, Daniel E. '58 GBA, undated (Box 48)
- Diamond, Edwin, undated (Box 48)
- Carroll, Diahann (Attended DGE in 1949), undated (Box 48)
- Diamond, Eugene B. '41 C., undated (Box 48)
- Diamond, Malcolm L., undated (Box 48)
- Diamond, Neil '60A, undated (Box 48)
- Diamond, Walter H., undated (Box 48)
- Diawara, Marthia, undated (Box 48)
- Diaz, Armando, undated (Box 48)
- Dibrell, James, undated (Box 48)
- Di Carlo, Dominick, undated (Box 48)
- Dick, William M., undated (Box 48)
- Dickerman, S(tuart) Carlton, undated (Box 48)
- Dickson, Robert E., undated (Box 48)
- Dickson, Samuel Heary, undated (Box 48)
- Dieckman, Katherine, undated (Box 48)
- Dierking, Edna, undated (Box 48)
- Di Franco, J Philip, undated (Box 48)
- Digangi, Charlis Esq., undated (Box 48)
- Digangi, Elizabeth Clarke '62W, '71 Ed., undated (Box 48)
- DiGiovanni, Mario '35E, undated (Box 48)
- Dill, William, undated (Box 48)
- Dillingham, Alice, undated (Box 48)
- Dilts, Marvin R., undated (Box 48)
- Dim, Joan Marans, undated (Box 48)
- Dimock, Dr. Marshall E.D, undated (Box 48)
- Dinallo, Eric R., undated (Box 48)
- Dinas, George C. '55, undated (Box 48)
- Dinces, Gale I., undated (Box 48)
- Diner, Hasia, undated (Box 48)
- Dinkins, David N., undated (Box 48)
- Director, William, undated (Box 48)
- Disch, Thomas, undated (Box 48)
- Distler, Theodore A. '22A, undated (Box 48)
- Father, Divine, undated (Box 49)
- Divita, Salvatore F., undated (Box 49)
- Divittorio, Myron, undated (Box 49)
- Dlamini, B.S., undated (Box 49)
- Dobbins, William E., undated (Box 49)
- Dobrow, Morris C., undated (Box 49)
- Doctorow, E.L., undated (Box 49)
- Dodge, Henry (DENTAL), undated (Box 49)
- Dodson, Dan W. '40 Ed., undated (Box 49)
- Dodson, Leon '67Ed., undated (Box 49)
- Doino, William D. '65 Law, undated (Box 49)
- Dolby, Kirkmon K.'73 GBA, undated (Box 49)
- Doll, Ronald C., undated (Box 49)
- Dolowich, Harry Solomon, undated (Box 49)
- Donie, Scott, undated (Box 49)
- Donis, Jack P., undated (Box 49)
- Donnellan, John J., undated (Box 49)
- Donohue, Andrew, undated (Box 49)
- Denis, Donoghue, undated (Box 49)
- Donovan, Dr. Bernard E., undated (Box 49)
- Donovan, Bernard '34ed '57ed, undated (Box 50)
- Donovan, Gerard 46L, undated (Box 50)
- Donovan, Hedley, undated (Box 50)
- Doran, Michael, undated (Box 50)
- Dorau, Herbert, undated (Box 50)
- Doremus, William L., undated (Box 50)
- Dorff, Jay, undated (Box 50)
- Dornfeld, Barry, undated (Box 50)
- Dorph, Martin, undated (Box 50)
- Dorsen, Norman, undated (Box 50)
- Dorsey, Jack, undated (Box 50)
- Dossick, Jesse, undated (Box 50)
- Doti, Maria I. '79W, '83G, undated (Box 50)
- Doubleday, Henry Grunwald, undated (Box 50)
- Doubrovsky, Serge, undated (Box 50)
- Douglas, Auron, undated (Box 50)
- Douglas, Charlotte, undated (Box 50)
- Douglass, David Bates, undated (Box 50)
- Douglas, Gordon W., undated (Box 50)
- Douglas, Linda, undated (Box 50)
- Doughty, Harold R., undated (Box 50)
- Douksza, John J., undated (Box 50)
- Dow, Robert B., undated (Box 50)
- Dowd, Kevin, undated (Box 50)
- Dowd, Daniel '38C., undated (Box 50)
- Dowell, Coleman, undated (Box 50)
- Downes, Chauncy, undated (Box 50)
- Downey, Morton Jr., undated (Box 50)
- Dowling, Herndon, undated (Box 50)
- Downing, Lester A., undated (Box 50)
- Dove, Walter M., undated (Box 50)
- Downs, Florence S., undated (Box 50)
- Downs, George, undated (Box 50)
- Downs, Robert Bingham, undated (Box 50)
- Doxiados, Constantinos, undated (Box 50)
- Drake, Ormond, undated (Box 50)
- Draper, Arthur S. '05E, undated (Box 51)
- Draper, Dorothy, undated (Box 51)
- Draper, John W., undated (Box 51)
- Draper, James F. '59 GBA, undated (Box 51)
- Draper, John C., undated (Box 51)
- Draper, William H. Jr. '46A, undated (Box 51)
- Dremuk, Richard, undated (Box 51)
- Drennen, Matthew Paul, undated (Box 51)
- Dresner, Jane S. '80 GBA, undated (Box 51)
- Dressner, Howard '40C, undated (Box 51)
- Dressner, Joe, undated (Box 51)
- Dressler, Ernestine, undated (Box 51)
- Dreyfuss, Rochelle, undated (Box 51)
- Dreyspool, A. Anthony, undated (Box 51)
- Driggs, Howard, undated (Box 51)
- Drillis, Rudolfs J., undated (Box 51)
- Dripps, Joseph Frederic Class of 1863, undated (Box 51)
- Driver, Sara, undated (Box 51)
- Druin, Allison, undated (Box 51)
- Drury, James '51-'51 Ed., undated (Box 51)
- Dryer, Lawrence S. '81, undated (Box 51)
- Drysdale, Thomas, undated (Box 51)
- Dryfoos, Robert J., undated (Box 51)
- Dubino, Peter, undated (Box 51)
- Dubois, R. Luke, undated (Box 51)
- Ducas, Dorothy, undated (Box 51)
- Duchin, Faye, undated (Box 51)
- Duckworth, Heather, undated (Box 51)
- Ducovny, Amram, undated (Box 51)
- Dudley, Jennifer, undated (Box 51)
- Duff, John Carr, undated (Box 51)
- Duffy, Niev J., undated (Box 51)
- Duggan, Lisa, undated (Box 51)
- Dukakis, Michael, undated (Box 51)
- Dumitriu, Iaona, undated (Box 52)
- Dumler, Martin G., undated (Box 52)
- Dumont, Allan E., undated (Box 52)
- Dumpson, Sames R., undated (Box 52)
- Dunbar, Howard, undated (Box 52)
- Dunbar, Rosalie, undated (Box 52)
- Duncan, Barbara, undated (Box 52)
- Duncan, Maria-Theresa, undated (Box 52)